<resources>

    <string name="help_headline">Help &#38; Knowledge</string>

    <string name="help_login_info_text">You are logged in with your mail %1$s.</string>
    <string name="help_logout_info_text">Your are logged out.</string>

    <string name="help_legal_headline">Legal Info</string>
    <string name="help_legal_terms_of_use">Terms of usage &#38; exclusion of liability claims</string>

    <string name="help_feedback_headline">Your Opinion</string>
    <string name="help_feedback_playstore">Rate us</string>
    <string name="help_feedback_googleplus">Give feedback or provide suggestions</string>

    <string name="help_about_headline">About the ShareWiFi App</string>
    <string name="help_about_version">Version %1$s</string>
    <string name="help_about_restart_info_tour">Restart the info tour</string>
    <string name="help_about_faq">Questions &#38; answers</string>

    <!-- FAQ -->

    <string name="help_q1">What does ShareWiFi offer?</string>
    <string name="help_a1"><b>Automatic connect with hotspots</b>
        You don\'t like to manually connect your devices with hotspots? Pretty cool, ShareWiFi is able
        to automatically connect you with shared hotspots. For sure you can enable or disable this
        feature using our settings.\n
        \n
        <b>Individual share of Wi-Fi credentials</b>
        Visitors want to have access to your internet? No problem, you can share your network individually.
        Your credentials keep invisible. The devices of your friends will automatically be connected by ShareWiFi.
        Undo sharing is always possible.\n
        \n
        <b>Once connected, always connected</b>
        Connecting your devices (smartphone, tablet, notebook, ...) with a hotspot again and again is terrifying.
        Using ShareWiFi you only have to connect one single device. All your other devices are managed by ShareWiFi.</string>

    <string name="help_q2">How can the sharing of networks be restricted?</string>
    <string name="help_a2">ShareWiFi never shares a network automatically. You can always specify
        the devices or users for a share.\n\nShareWiFi allows to share networks in three ways:\n
        &#8226; <b>Device Share</b>\n All your devices (where you are logged in) have access to the Wi-Fi credentials.\n
        &#8226; <b>Group Share</b> All the users you select have access to the shared Wi-Fi network.\n
        &#8226; <b>Global Share</b> Everybody have access to the shared Wi-Fi network.\n\n
        <b>Remember that you are only allowed to share networks with confirmation of a network\'s owner.
            Else you infringes our <![CDATA[<a href="">terms of usage</a>]]>.</b></string>
    <string name="help_q3">What happens when I share a network?</string>
    <string name="help_a3">First, the Wi-Fi credentials are encrypted and transmitted to our server. Here they are stored encrypted.\n
        Next, they are decrypted and reencrypted for each device that has access (specified inside your share).
        Afterwards, the credentials are transmitted to these devices and stored inside the local ShareWiFi database.
        Also they are stored inside the Android network storage during the ShareWiFi app is running.
        This is necessary for the feature to undo the share.</string>


</resources>